acuitylaser.com 2015-11-14

# Acuity Laser's Privacy Policy | Learn About Laser Measuring Devices

Home > Privacy Policy

## Acuity Protects Your Information That It Collects On This Website

**Effective April 22, 2011**

Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:

  * Our Commitment To Privacy
  * The Information We Collect
  * How We Use Information
  * Our Commitment To Data Security
  * Our Commitment To Children's Privacy
  * How To Access Or Correct Your Information
  * How To Contact Us

### Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

### The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Acuity website. On some pages, you can make requests and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

  * Name
  * Company Name
  * Address
  * Email address
  * Phone number

### The Way We Use Information

We use the information you provide about yourself for company marketing purposes only. We do not share this information with outside parties except our international sales partners. It is likely that we will attempt to contact you by e-mail or telephone to discuss your requirements for our laser sensor products.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

You can register with our website if you would like to receive our newsletter as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

### Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### Our Commitment To Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

### How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You may contact us and request that we change your information in our databases.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

### How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 503-227-5178 or send us an email.

DOWNLOADSLiterature & Software

NEW PRODUCT

NEW DEVICE:AR2000 Laser Distance Meter

The AR2000 specializes in measurement of hot surfaces, including hot, glowing steel. It is also excellent at measuring outdoors and in bright light conditions.

Learn More
